That has
happened
Om Om
[Music]
Hello friends, a very warm welcome to all of
you on my YouTube channel. I am
your help consultant Kajal. Today in this video I will discuss
two health
insurance plans which are Care
Plan and Ergo Health Suraksha Pramukh. If
you are on my channel for the first time then please
subscribe to my channel.
Please like my videos and press the bell icon so that
you will keep getting video recordings in the latest updates. So let's start the
video. First of all we will talk
about these plans and the news options. In both the plans, you get
time options ranging from Rs 3 lakh to Rs 75 lakh.
Now let's talk about the free
health check-up in this policy. In the Care Plan, if
you are below 18 years of age, then you do
not need to get a medical check-up done. Whereas
in the HDFC Ergo Suraksha Plan, if
you are below 47 years of age, then you do
not need to get a free medical check-up done.
Now let's know how many charges will be there in these plans if you get a
free health check-up done. So,
Care
If your policy is accepted, there is
no cost for a free health checkup. However, if your policy is
rejected,
50% of the premium will be deducted.
For those who have had their tests done, you should know about this unique
Suraksha plan, a free health
check-up course.
If you get an Islamic free health checkup,
you will have to pay 50% at St. Paul's for your test. If your
test is rejected, you will have to pay 100%
of the cost for the free health checkup.
Now let's talk
about the treatment. So, in the Clear
plan, you get 541 Discover
and such a Protector plan,
you will get more reduction cover.
Regarding the conspiracy expenses, so
care friends, you get free medical
expenses cover for 30 days and
post-graduation expenses cover for
7 days.
In such an amazing Suraksha plan,
you get huge additional expenses cover
for the scriptures and  Post Graduation
Express You have to, firstly,
talk about Delhi alarms for good days, then
in the Care Plan you have to
install Capsicum and in such a shallow security plan,
you get hospital cash benefit
only after paying extra premium, but your
hospitalization should be for minimum 24 hours
and maximum up to one day, you get
hospital cash benefit
and if you are admitted in ICU, then
you do
not get such amazing security plan with double hospital cash, as per
selected Islam Pinjore, which
you get minimum ₹1000 and maximum ₹5000,
now you get no claim bonus, so
in this Remedy Super Plan you get a
Nokia phone of 150 pcs
and in such a person, now in Help Tree
Alarm, you get an increase of 10 to 25
percent on every shot
in every year, which goes up to a maximum of 50 to 50 persons,
in Family Health Checkup Care Plan with the benefit of Extended Due Relative Bonus  You get this every year
without any relations and in such an Alcohol
Suraksha Plan you
get the benefit of preventive health checkup booster every
year to Amritsar also in Treatment Care Plan
you are covered up to ten percent Avdhesh
Mishra and Residential Debate Protector Language
you are covered for office recruitment now because in
Sanjha Organ Donor Expenses Care Name
you are covered minimum up to 50 thousand and maximum up to 1
lakh and in HDFC Ergo
Suraksha Plan you are covered for Organ Donor
Expenses in front of you
Ambulance Charges Care Plan this
covers you up to ₹3000 per week addition
and HDFC Ergo Suraksha Plan
you will get road ambulance charges as per the policy which is rich in taste
and at
present from ₹2000 to maximum 15065 and
its comprehensive ambulance is also covered for
such person Suraksha Golden Platinum
Plinth Beam up to five oaths and
about domestic flight Care
Friends you are covered 10 Tamil Saath
and HTC and that is Suraksha Plan I will give
you committee shot  Deewan's valid cover
is for Ayush Treatment Care and HDFC Ergo
Suraksha is also covered for tens of thousands.
After completion of the treatment in the New Born Baby Care Plan, you can send your voicemail
and edit, share and
in the Suraksha Plan, you have to pay the baby by the time the
Panchvati is covered. Open the Airplane App
Bluetooth Settings
and get the
second medical opinion when the elephant is
not available in the SDOP Arghya Daan App. So this is also a little information
about the Care Plan and such Arghya Suraksha Plan. To get more information about this, you
can connect with us with the help of the WhatsApp number you are seeing on the screen now.
If you found this video really useful, then
please subscribe to my channel,
please like my video and press the bell icon so
that you get the latest updates
regarding my videos.
Thank you for watching it first in Hindi.